<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GOSemSim</title>
    <link>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/GOSemSim/</link>
    <description>Recent content on GOSemSim</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the Artistic-2.0 license</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 12:08:13 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://guangchuangyu.github.io/GOSemSim/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GOSemSim: GO semantic similarity measurement</title>
      <link>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/GOSemSim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 12:08:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/GOSemSim/</guid>
      <description>The semantic comparisons of Gene Ontology (GO) annotations provide quantitative ways to compute similarities between genes and gene groups, and have became important basis for many bioinformatics analysis approaches. GOSemSim is an R package for semantic similarity computation among GO terms, sets of GO terms, gene products and gene clusters. GOSemSim implemented five methods proposed by Resnik, Schlicker, Jiang, Lin and Wang respectively.
GOSemSim is released within the Bioconductor project and the source code is hosted on  GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/GOSemSim/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/GOSemSim/documentation/</guid>
      <description>Vignettes  An introduction to GOSemSim    Blog posts  News and updates  GOSemSim an R package for measuring semantic similarity among GO terms and gene products proper use of GOSemSim BioC 3.1: NEWS of my BioC packages BioC 3.2: NEWS of my BioC packages BioC 3.3: NEWS of my BioC packages BioC 3.4: NEWS of my BioC packages    Applications  using GOSemSim to rank proteins obtained by co-IP   Find out more on https://guangchuangyu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Featured Articles</title>
      <link>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/GOSemSim/featured-articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/GOSemSim/featured-articles/</guid>
      <description>Let us know if you have published using GOSemSim and your publication will be featured here.
Disease or Drug analysis  Regulatory T Cells Orchestrate Similar Immune Evasion of Fetuses and Tumors in Mice. The Journal of Immunology. 2016, 196(2):678-690. DOSE: an R/Bioconductor package for disease ontology semantic and enrichment analysis. Bioinformatics. 2015, 31(4):608-609. TFmiR: a web server for constructing and analyzing disease-specific transcription factor and miRNA co-regulatory networks. Nucleic Acids Research.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>